<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Extra Psycasts (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ExtraPsycasts</packageId>
  <author>chromiumboy</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ExtraPsycasts</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</packageId>
      <displayName>Royalty</displayName>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of chromiumboys mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2099341696

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ExtraPsycasts][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Requires the Royalty Expansion for Rimworld.

Adds a collection of 11 new psycasts to the Rimworld Royalty Expansion. These new abilities can be granted by upgrading a psychic amplifier and by obtaining the appropriate psytrainer through quest rewards or trading

These extra psycasts include

- Accelerate healing (Rank 1 psycast). Increases the rate at which a target's injuries heal and the rate infection immunity is gained.
- Pyrokinesis (Rank 1 psycast). Starts a small fire at a target location. Does not require line of sight.
- Precognition (Rank 2 psycast). Increases the psycaster's accuracy in combat and their melee dodge chance.
- Soothe mind (Rank 2 psycast). Provides a target with positive moodlet, and snaps them out of any mental breaks they may be experiencing.
- Fortitude (Rank 3 psycast). The target receives much less damage than usual.
- Stasis (Rank 3 psycast). A friendly target goes into coma-like state. The rate at which their needs deplete will drastically slow, as will bleeding.
- Telepathic link (Rank 3 psycast). The psycaster and a friendly target share some of the experience they gain with each other.
- Cognitive enhancement (Rank 4 psycast). Increases the rate at which a friendly target is able to research.
- Energise (Rank 4 psycast). Increases the movement speed of a friendly target and the rate at which they prefom manual labour.
- Sense thoughts (Rank 4 psycast). Improves the performance of the psycaster in social encounters and when bartering.
- Psychic lance (Rank 5 psycast). Deals damage directly to the target's brain (affects both organic and electronic brains).

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2560684411][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ExtraPsycasts?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.1</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>